A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991, RG 39 FA1505
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991; 39; 234.9 Cubic Feet 597 containers
  - Miscellaneous Ephemera, 1940-1988; 39; 2.1 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box and 2 oversize boxes
    - Order of St. Anna,, Cross and Star with Diamonds (Orders given to Paul Ehrlich) - Case Only (Box 594, Folder 10)
      Case only.
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Ramon Magsaysay Award Foundation - Resolution (Box 595)
    - Investment funds, circa 1940-1958 (Box 596)
  - Audiovisual Materials, 1987-1991; 40; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    Sound recordings; Moving Images
    - Arts - National Committee for the Vatican Judaica Exhibition - "A Visual Testimony: Judaica from the Vatican Library", 1987 May; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11955)
      Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - Arts - Japan Art Association - "The Establishment of Praemium Imperiale", VHS, NTSC (Box 1, Tape AV 11956)
    - Arts - Libraries - Library of Congress - "Memory and Imagination: New Pathways to the Library of Congress", VHS; 58 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11957)
    - Arts - Museums - Smithsonian Institution - J. Carter Brown Speech, National Press Club Luncheon, 1989 June 20; Sound, 47 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15316)
      Part 1: Introduction/Speech (28 minutes). Part 2: Question and Answer (19 minutes)
    - Arts - Music - Carnegie Hall Society - Dalrymple Productions - "Carnegie Hall's Restoration - The 28 Week Miracle", 1988 June 1; VHS; 28 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11958)
      Television documentary which tells tells the story of the music hall's restoration. Aired on Channel 13 (PBS-TV) on June 9, 1988 at 9:30 PM.
    - Civic - "The Paris Liberty Flame", International Herald Tribune, 1989 May 10; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11960)
    - Civic - Starserve: A Project of the Kraft General Foods Foundation - "Interview with Mike Love", 1991 April 6; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11961)
      WABC-TV News at 7:30, Starserve Santa Monica, CA
    - Raleigh Tavern Society - "A Tradition of Philanthropy", VHS; 12 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11962)
    - National Geographic Television, "Survivors of Skeleton Coast", VHS; 57 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11963)
    - Education - Colleges - United Negro College Fund - "United Negro College Fund Presents Campaign 2000: An Investment in America's Future", 1990; VHS; 11 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11964)
      New York Television, Inc. (NYTV)
    - Education - Colleges - University of Louisville - Joel Elkes - "Arts in Medicine Program, Division of Attitudinal and Behavioral Medicine, University of Louisville, KY, VHS; 23 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11965)
    - Education - Colleges - University of Louisville - Health Awareness Workshop, VHS; 19 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11966)
    - Education - Foundations - George C. Marshall Foundation - "George C. Marshall - American Leadership", VHS; 12 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11967)
    - American Soviet Youth Orchestra - July 19, Bolshoi Hall, Moscow State Conservatory (Global American Television), VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11968)
    - Chico Mendes: Voice of the Amazon, VHS; 56 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11969)
    - Up With People: 25th Anniversary Highlights, VHS; 11 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11970)
    - Medicine - Institute for Humanistic Science - "Biobehavioral Systems", VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11971)
    - Medicine - Juvenile Diabetes Foundation - "The Only Remedy Is A Cure", VHS; 7 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11972)
    - New York Republican State Committee, 1989 October 13; VHS; 6 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11973)
    - "An Introduction to Contemplative Visions", Winters Productions, 1990 November 30 (date stamp); VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11974)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Memorial Foundation - "Coolidge Preview" - Archival Film Samples, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11975)
    - Winrock International Conference Center, 1989 October 12; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11976)
    - Valley Ranch New Room Construction, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11977)
      To: Mrs. Jean Branscombe. From: Dick Long.
    - Covenant House - Awards Dinner, VHS; 12 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11978)
    - Youth - Homes - WPIX - "The Best Talk in Town", The Children's Village, 1988 Spring; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11979)